<resources>
    <string name="app_name">10 Must see Places in India </string>

    <string name="string0"><b>1. Pangong Lake, Ladakh India</b><p> - Transporting you to an ethereal place, the Pangong Lake is located in Ladakh. This is a place where unblemished azure water is fringed by rugged mountains while cotton candy clouds float above. Feel the serenity and magic envelope you!</p> </string>
    <string name="string1"><b>2. Rafting and Camping in Rishikesh</b><p> - With bursting of vitality and eagerness, twenties is the best time to indulge in adventure sports. Ride the mystical waters of Ganges with rafting in Rishikesh, which is the most famous place for this adrenaline pumping sport.</p></string>
    <string name="string2"><b>3. Living Root Bridges, Meghalaya</b><p> - What seems to appear straight out of a fantasy movie, the Living Root Bridges have to be seen to be believed! Some of these roots are more than hundred feet long and are strong enough to carry the weight of fifty people at one time.</p></string>
    <string name="string3"><b>4. Chadar – The Frozen River Trek</b><p> - How often does one boast about walking on a frozen river in a dreamlike destination? Stamped as one of the most thrilling experiences for an adventure aficionado, the Chadar trek route connects villages in the Zanskar valley.</p></string>
    <string name="string4"><b>5. Andaman Islands, Scuba Diving Exploring the Coral Reefs</b><p> - The rich reefs will surprise you with their varied offerings. Colourful fish, sunken ships, prismatic sea life and some steeply undulating hills of raven volcanic lava, makes for an unusual diving experience.</p></string>
    <string name="string5"><b>6. Manali-Leh Road Trip</b><p> - The Manali-Leh Highway has always been a favourite. Be it for the groups or solo travellers, this route outshines any other backpacking trips in India. All -you need to do: get geared up for some adventure, hit the road and reach nowhere! </p></string>
    <string name="string6"><b>7.  Manali, Himachal Pradesh</b><p> - Let your imagination take flight as you look at nature in its entire splendor. Be treated to a spectacular view of the Solang Valley as you soar in the sky. In seconds you’ll have your adrenaline rush and you’ll be spellbound. </p></string>
    <string name="string7"><b>8. Rann of Kutch, Gujarat</b><p> - Imagine nothingness and then imagine it some more! Being one of the remote places in India and the largest salt desert in the world, the Rann of Kutch comes to life somewhere in October as the otherwise watered locale begins to dry up. Try making it to Kala Dungar.</p></string>
    <string name="string8"><b>9. Sandakphu, Darjeeling</b><p> - Among the 5 highest peaks in the world, Sandakphu makes for a dreamy location. Surreal natural beauty and spectacular views define this place. It is here one can spot around 600 myriad orchid-varieties and a remarkable diversity in nature.</p></string>
    <string name="string9"><b>10. Tawang Town, Arunachal Pradesh</b><p> - Moving onto the North Eastern part of India, you will find one of the most serene and magnificent hill stations. Tawang, a sparsely populated hill town in Arunachal Pradesh also outshines other hill stations in India. </p></string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
